<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="https://procoder.io/rss/"><channel><title>Pro Coder</title><description>Actionable Advice to Accelerate Your Career</description><link>https://dev.procoder.io</link><language>en-us</language><item><title>Making rookie mistakes</title><link>https://dev.procoder.io/newsletters/2025-01-05-making-rookie-mistakes</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.procoder.io/newsletters/2025-01-05-making-rookie-mistakes</guid><description>...and surviving them!</description><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Hey Greg,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a pro coder, I made a terrible rookie mistake!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was really embarrassing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just spent three days tracking down why my website wouldn’t let me enter edit mode… but my wife’s would!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turns out that on Cloudflare I had enabled “Rocket Loader”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I use Cloudflare because it has superior DNS management and lots of other great features.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I assumed that Rocket Loader was another great tool to deploy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turns out it was kind of like going into your Gentoo Linux machine and rebuilding everything with maximum GCC optimization switched on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Might speed things up. But probably won’t work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The webpage when I’d click “Edit” (i used Divi on all my websites), the edit spinner would pop up…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;…and just keep spinning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I disabled almost every plug-in I had on my website trying to figure out what had broken things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking of breaking things and putting them back together, check out the sponsor of this article…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:0.95em;color:rgb(9,194,105);&quot;&gt;Today’s sponsor…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div style=&quot;display:flex;align-items:center;gap:2em;margin:6px&quot;&gt;
  &lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;div style=&quot;flex:1;&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;A smart person learns from their mistakes. A WISE person learns from OTHER people&apos;s mistakes.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Grab &lt;strong&gt;&lt;i&gt;12 Rules For Pro Coders&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; and learn from MY mistakes with actionable advice to accelerate your career!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;a href=&quot;/12-rules/offer&quot; style=&quot;display:inline-block;padding:0.5em 1em;background:#2d8cff;color:#fff;border-radius:4px;text-decoration:none;font-weight:bold;&quot;&gt;
      GET YOUR COPY NOW!
    &lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;div style=&quot;flex:1;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img __ASTRO_IMAGE_=&quot;{&amp;#x22;src&amp;#x22;:&amp;#x22;@assets/images/books/12RulesforProCoders_Medium.jpg&amp;#x22;,&amp;#x22;alt&amp;#x22;:&amp;#x22;&amp;#x22;,&amp;#x22;index&amp;#x22;:0}&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had even switched to “development mode” on Cloudflare!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turns out that knob doesn’t disable EVERYTHING.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Truth is…I went too fast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I kicked myself knowing I had just made this newbie mistake. I shook my head, upset with myself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had switched on Rocket Loader along with a few other optimizations without verifying it worked let alone sped things up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And that was my fault.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a pro coder we just always slow down and do things one step at a time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Test one thing and verify it works.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then test another thing. And another. And another.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being a pro coder means taking your time and doing it correctly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A series of correctly done steps and people that don’t code will thing your some kind if frickin’ genius. But you’re just moving things forward one step at a
time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s easy to say but this process requires discipline and commitment. Don’t make the mistake I made.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Test your changes. One by one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re a pro coder or plan to become one then stay tuned for my next article. But if you simply can’t wait then check out this video and learn what your most
valuable resource is when it comes to being a pro coder!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;— Greg&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P.S. Consider &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtube.com/@ProCoderIO/join&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;becoming a PREMIUM member&lt;/a&gt; if you want first dibs on EVERYTHING! I’ve already
shared all this with my members, as it happened, and I appreciate all
the support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style=&quot;margin-top:2em;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=msbZyMAjSYM&quot;&gt;
                    &lt;img src=&quot;https://img.youtube.com/vi/msbZyMAjSYM/hqdefault.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Watch on YouTube&quot; style=&quot;width:100%;height:auto;border:0;&quot; /&gt;
                    &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded><media:content type="image/jpeg" width="800" height="457" medium="image" url="https://dev.procoder.io//_astro/1_xI1AopY1TeWfWCdgXcWK0Q.CcZ3tk0K.jpeg"/></item></channel></rss>